# Iyris P. Vigil

604 -704 -2632

iyrisvigil@gmail.com

in /iyris

/iyriss

/iyris.myportfolio.com

#### **SUMMARY**

A full stack web developer with a background in graphic design and marketing, I've always liked the idea behind bringing life to static designs. My approach to coding centers around a smooth user experience and I enjoy the process of moving from design to implementation.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Easy Ride**

Working project for the Victoria Therapeutic Riding Association to manage users, horses, and bookings for rides, events, and lessons. (React, Rails, Axios, Material UI, PostgreSQL)

#### Wiki Maps

A web app that allows users to create and browse maps with a list of favorite points (EJS, jQuery, SASS, NodeJS, Express, Javascript, PostgreSQL)

#### **Tweeter**

Single-page responsive Twitter clone ( HTML, CSS, Javascript, AJAX, Node, Express)

#### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS, SASS, Ruby, SQL.

Frameworks, Libraries and Environments: Node.js, React, Rails, Ajax,

Express, EJS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Material UI.

**Systems, CMS and Databases:** Git, PostgreSQL, Wordpress.

**Testing:** Cypress, Mocha/Chai, Storybook, Jest, RSpec.

Adobe Creative Cloud: Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, XD, After Effects,

Premiere Pro.

Spoken Languages: English, German, Spanish.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Education Coach and Marketing Assistant** *Next Goal Agency*

Vancouver, BC

Oct 2019 – April 2020

- Created engaging image and video content for social media accounts and website.
- Helped managing website content for SEO.
- Communicated with potential immigration and education clients.

### Digital Marketing Assistant Smart Web Canada

Vancouver, BC

Sept 2018 – May 2019

- Optimized client websites for search engines through analysis content, keywords and Title and Meta tags.
- Introduced social media scheduling.
- Wrote and maintained social media posts calendar for clients on a weekly basis.
- Created content for email marketing campaigns with Mailchimp

### Sales and Marketing Intern

Gran Canaria, Spain

Seaside Hotels, S.L.

July 2015 – October 2015

- Processed weekly sales reports, board and sales preview statistics.
- Organised marketing plans to develop strategies and processed office correspondence in English, German and Spanish.
- Database maintenance and merchandise inventory management.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Lighthouse Labs** 

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Vancouver, BC

**British Columbia Institute of Technology** 

Jan 2018 - June 2019

Media Techniques and Marketing Comms Certificate

Vancouver, BC

**SELC Career College** 

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017

Business Foundations and Communications

Vancouver, BC

**University of Applied Sciences Salzburg** 

B.A. in Business Innovation and Management

Oct 2013 - Nov 2016

Salzburg, Austria